janyaa.org 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy – Janyaa

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy of Janyaa, LLC. (“we”, “us”, “our”) applies to the operations of Janyaa that we offer through our website janyaa.org, and the mobile software applications Janyaa, (collectively the “Service”). It provides the policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing the information of each visitor to or user of the Service (“you”, “your”, or the “User”). We recognize that you choose to use the Service and we consider your privacy and the security of your personal information to be very important. We appreciate your trust in maintaining the security of your personal information, and we want you to know what information we collect and why.

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we make reference to your Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) that we collect. This denotes information about you as an individual, such that your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your name, home address and home telephone number are examples of PII.

There occur certain interactions within the Service, such as choosing to receive email updates or text notifications, for which we collect information necessary to undertake such actions (e.g. name, email address, mobile phone number). If you prefer not to disclose PII, you can still enjoy other areas of the Service, however we may collect additional information that is not personally identifying (“Non-PII”). “Cookies” and your Internet Protocol (IP) Address are examples of Non-PII, and they are discussed in further detail below.

By using the Service, you accept the practices set forth in this Privacy Policy. Please read it carefully before using the Service. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not access or otherwise use the Service. The Service is also subject to the TERMS OF USE.

#### Information We Collect

We receive and store information you give us when you use the Service. You provide such information when you visit, sign up for, login to, operate, or otherwise use the Service or contact us. For example, we collect information when you: contact us from the web site, provide information to sign up for an account with the Service, provide information in Your Account / Profile; send us email requests for products or communicate with us by email for any auxiliary purpose; login and operate your account within the Service, or utilize Personal Notification Services. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you might not be able to use many of the Service features.

We use the information that you provide us to: fulfill transactions; operate the Service; respond to your requests; improve our Service, and; communicate with you. We DO NOT sell your PII to third parties or mass marketers. Unless you consent to the disclosure of your PII, only Janyaa and our affiliates, technical consultants, third-party administrators and other third parties who make our Service available, enhance its functionality, or provide associated services, have access to this information. For example, we may work with agents to analyze data, operate promotions, provide marketing assistance, and/or provide customer service. They have access to information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

We collect general, non-personal, statistical information (i.e. Non-PII) about the use of the Service. We employ first-party cookies and use Factual and Google Analytics to gather anonymous information about our users and their interactions with the Service. Examples include the capture of visitors’ IP addresses, computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, how long visitors stay on a specific page, and which hyperlinks and any areas of pages that visitors “click” on. We use this information in the aggregate to compile data trends, define most popular areas of interest, and otherwise analyze the performance of our Service. This aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to the Sites. An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web, and can be used to identify your computer. However, when we collect IP addresses and do so in an aggregate fashion, this occurs in a way that does not identify you personally.

As you browse our sites, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. We use third-party cookies (such as Google’s DoubleClick cookie) to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our site (commonly known as ‘Remarketing’). We also employ Google’s Interest-based advertising and 3rd party audience data (such as age, gender and interest) with Google Analytics for product development purposes. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

While using the Service, you have the option to engage with a Janyaa representative either by email or phone call. Should you choose to participate in an email or live call, for the purpose of improving our service and assisting you appropriately, the email exchange and/or phone call is logged and we may collect information such as your email address, phone number, language, etc., and any live conversations may also be recorded for on-going training and service level purposes.

While using the Service, you may have opportunities to post information in public forums. Be advised that any information you personally submit, whether PII or Non-PII, is made public and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for any third party’s use of PII that you may publicly disclose through the Service.

#### Account Creation

#### Requesting an Account and Setup

Should you request an account with the Service, Janyaa requires that you submit a First and Last Name, Email Address, a Personal Description (e.g. Restaurant Owner), level of service requested, credit card information for service billing, and a Restaurant Name, Street Address, City, State, and Zip Code, plus other optional information. Janyaa requires this information to create and manage new Accounts. Janyaa Account Holders receive a username and password to access specific features within the Service. Janyaa adds the email address of Account Holders to an Account Holder only email list. Such list is used for periodic product updates as well as Service-Account updates that may include, but are not limited to, notices required by law and/or notices of a change in our TERMS OF USE and this Privacy Policy. Account Holders may opt-out of receiving product updates, however Account Holders may not opt-out of receiving the Service-Account email updates.

Janyaa also adds the email address, submitted during an account service request, to a Client Email List. The Client Email List is unique to the account, and is delivered regularly after operational use of an account with the Service. The User may add additional email addresses to this Client Email list, and the User and any additional Users added may opt-out of this Client Email List.

#### Operational Activity Data Collection

If you hold an account with the Service, Janyaa may track your operational transaction activity. Janyaa records transactions that occur through Account Activity on the Service, including but not limited to: adding a guest (including all information submitted as part of adding a guest), making guest edits, notifying a guest, seating a guest, and messaging activity in the account. Janyaa records and has access to settings changes you may make in your Account, such as seating areas, server names, location addresses, area code settings, notes settings, paging settings, and email addresses listed in the Janyaa Hostess, Janyaa Admin and Client Email List.

#### How Janyaa Uses This Data

Rest assured that Janyaa will not publish any User’s operational transaction or account settings data in any personally identifiable way. We will not sell your personal information to anyone. Janyaa uses your personal transaction data to create statistics that are unique to your account and that are included in the Janyaa Services and Client Email. Janyaa uses transaction and account data in the aggregate to monitor trends, run reports, define most popular areas of interest, and otherwise analyze the performance of the Service. Janyaa may, and reserves the right to, publish, share, or sell this anonymous statistical data in the aggregate form with third parties. Rest assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to or users of the Service.

#### Cookies

Like many web sites, the Service may transfer cookies to your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that function with your web browser and that enable our systems to recognize it and improve your use of the Service. For example, cookies may enable us to recognize your specific browser and offer you a personalized greeting when you use the Service or to inform us of what browser you are using. The Help function on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, display a notification that your browser is receiving new cookies, erase cookies, or disable cookies altogether. We recommend that you permit cookies from our Service because in many instances cookies allow you to make use of many of the Service features.

#### Links to Other Sites

The Service may, on occasion, provide links that direct you away from the Service to another website. These third-party websites are not operated by us and are beyond our control. We do not share any of your PII with these websites. These websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data, or solicit personal information. When visiting these websites, you are subject to their privacy policies, and we encourage you to read them as well as any terms of use or service. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites and we cannot guarantee the security of any of your PII collected there. Addresses or content of these websites may change without prior notice, however when we become aware of these changes, we may remove links to websites that no longer meet our approval.

#### Disclosure of Your Information

We reserve the right to release account and other PII when: we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; at the request of any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding such as a subpoena; to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any law, rule or regulation; protect the rights, property, or safety of the Service, our users, or others, or; to enforce or apply ourTERMS OF USE and other agreements.

#### Business Transfers

As our business continues to grow, we may acquire or sell a business. We reserve the right to transfer customer information in connection with such a transaction, but such information remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. In the event that Janyaa or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

#### Choices You Have

You can always choose not to share certain information with us, even though it may not allow you to access many of the Service features. You can add or update personal information within your account, and you can disable cookies as discussed above.  
By electing to receive emails and text messages from us, you permit us to send you exclusive information and special offers that you may otherwise not learn about. If at any time you desire to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from us, you can choose to “opt-out” of these emails or text messages by following the instructions located at the bottom of these emails or text messages.

#### Children

Individuals of age 13-17 may visit the websites of the Service, but they may do so only with the involvement of a parent or legal guardian, and subject to our TERMS OF USE. As per these Terms, persons under the age of 13 are not permitted to access the Service. We do not intentionally seek to sell anything to, influence, collect information from or otherwise address individuals 13 years of age and younger, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 through the Service.

#### Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

The use of the Service, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to our TERMS OF USE, including limitation of damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Delaware. If you have any concern about privacy at our Service, please CONTACT US and we will try to address your concerns.

As our business evolves and our practices change, we will continue to update this Privacy Policy. We may periodically email notifications of changes in our policies, unless you have instructed us not to do so, but you should check our Service frequently for any changes. Your continued use of the Service assents your agreement to these changes.
